<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Vincent's Personal Page</title><link>https://leroyvn.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Vincent's Personal Page</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-UK</language><copyright>Copyright © 2021, Vincent Leroy.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 11:30:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://leroyvn.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Using Nox with PDM</title><link>https://leroyvn.github.io/blog/nox_pdm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 11:30:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://leroyvn.github.io/blog/nox_pdm/</guid><description>Nox and PDM are both fantastic Python development tools. However, their opposite stances towards virtual environment usage makes using them together a little more cumbersome. In this note, I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how I integrated Nox in my PDM workflow.
We will use Nox to automate testing on multiple Python versions during CI. We&amp;rsquo;d also like to run our tests using a similar command locally without having to maintain almost duplicate Nox sessions.</description></item><item><title>Conda Workflow</title><link>https://leroyvn.github.io/blog/conda_workflow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 11:44:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://leroyvn.github.io/blog/conda_workflow/</guid><description>This page describes my Conda workflow.
Conda I use Conda as my environment and package manager. This choice is the outcome of a long professional history. Pros for choosing Conda:
it&amp;rsquo;s portable; it&amp;rsquo;s simple to use; it provides optimised binaries for several scientific packages; it saves space on my hard drive; it can install more than just Python stuff. Cons:
many packages are missing (and interoperability with Pip has many issues when one starts playing with dependency pinning); usually second-class citizen in CI workflows (see also previous point about deps pinning); Conda&amp;rsquo;s dependency resolution is slow; many people don&amp;rsquo;t use Conda.</description></item></channel></rss>